mynameart.com 2015-06-02

# Privacy Policy | MyNameArt

## Personal Detail

We respect the privacy of every individual who visits the website. We may collect personal identification information from users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.

We will never pass on your personal details (selling, renting or otherwise) to anyone. The following legal document will dictate how we will handle this information. This privacy policy together with our terms of use sets out mynameart.com will use any personal data we collect from you, or you provide to us during your use of the online service(www.mynameart.com).

mynameart.com may collect and use users personal information for the following purposes:  
  **\- To personalize user experience :** We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.   
  **\- To send periodic emails :** User they will receive emails that may include news about mynameart, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the user would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

## Non Personal Detail

We may autimatically collect your non personal information about you during the service such as type of browser you use you ip address. This information is only used to improve our service on the website. You can not be identified any of this information.

## Cookies

We may collect information about your computer such as your IP adress, cookies, operating System, browser you use for website(www.mynameart.com).

This website uses cookies. A cookie is a small, removable data file that is stored by your web browser on your computer. Cookies allow you to place an order on this Website and allow us to enhance, facilitate and personalize your online surfing and shopping experience. For example, we use cookies to: 

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

  * Remember your stored preferences on this Website.
  * Present relevant content to you when you visit this Website.
  * Analyze visitor behavior and
  * Facilitate other similar type of activities.

## Link And Advertisement 

Our website may contain link of our partner website, advertise and affiliates, we use google adsense so some of the ads may be served by google. Googles user DART cookie enable it to serve to user based on their visit to our website(www.mynameart.com) and other internet website. Affiliates and advertiser have their own privacy policy so we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

## Contact US 

For use website(www.mynameart.com) you have to acceptance our privacy policy. If you do not agree to this privacy policy then please do not use our website(www.mynameart.com). If you have any query regarding privacy policy and any content in website then please kindly contact us at info@mynameart.com
